{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "What is the Chinese name for Horse Stance in Taijiquan?",
      "choice1": "Ma Bu",
      "choice2": "Gong JianBu",
      "choice3": "Zuo Pan Bu",
      "choice4": "Si Liu Bu",
      "answer": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Horse stance was developed and practiced by ___________.",
      "choice1": "artist",
      "choice2": "horse Rider",
      "choice3": "Martial Artist and Warriors",
      "choice4": "Players",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The monks of Shaolin Temple recognize the importance of strong foundation and developed the Horse Stance as a way to ________ and __________.",
      "choice1": "Physical, emotional",
      "choice2": "Cultivate physical, mental strength",
      "choice3": "mental health",
      "choice4": "Physical Touch",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the primary purposes of the Horse Stance?",
      "choice1": "Widening Legs",
      "choice2": "To develop Muscle Legs",
      "choice3": "Just to exercise",
      "choice4": "To develop Physical Strength and endurance",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What requires to hold the Horse Stance",
      "choice1": "Breathing",
      "choice2": "Concentration",
      "choice3": "Standing",
      "choice4": "Techniques",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Horse Stance in Martial Arts",
      "choice1": "Timeless and Foundational Posture",
      "choice2": "Hard Stance",
      "choice3": "Defense",
      "choice4": "All of the Above",
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "It is serves as a training tool for developing physical and mental attributes.",
      "choice1": "Four-Six Stance",
      "choice2": "False Stance",
      "choice3": "Bow-Arrow Stance",
      "choice4": "Horse Stance",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the right standing posture of Horse Stance?",
      "choice1": "The feet wider than shoulder-width apart, with the knees bent and the thighs parallel to the ground.",
      "choice2": "The feet is wider enough.",
      "choice3": "The back is straight",
      "choice4": "Balance",
      "answer": 1
    },

    {
      "question": "The arms can be positioned in various way depending on the ___________.",
      "choice1": "Martial Arts style.",
      "choice2": "Techniques being practiced.",
      "choice3": "A and B",
      "choice4": "None of the Above",
      "answer": 3
    },

    {
      "question": "It generate power and maintain balance. What Horse Stance provides?",
      "choice1": "Stable Base of executing strikes",
      "choice2": "All of the Above",
      "choice3": "Kicks and blocks",
      "choice4": "To generate power and maintain balance",
      "answer": 3
    }
  ]
}